Heat. Heat.
Heat. Hey. Hey. Hey. Heat.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Hello.
Oh, does it work. Am I live?
Please tell me I'm live again.
I'm having so much technical issues
today.
Unfortunate
sometimes
and he's alive.
Hello.
Hope I'm audible.
Hope I'm even
I Oh no.
H. Am I live again? Oh my god.
Am I live again? Oh my god.
So much technical issues.
That is a
Oh my god.
What the
And then it can Can you work for me?
Come on. Come on. Okay. I think I'm
live.
I suppose
I am.
Yeah.
Hi. Uh,
let me see.
Okay, this works.
Sorry everyone.
How is the life? How's everyone been
lately?
I'm going to go out right now. I was
inside my room apart.
Actually, I just came in
a few minutes ago.
Um, and just thought of
um doing the stream today because
outside it's so cold outside.
freezing cold,
but
it's a good vibe outside.
And I wanted to uh enjoy that vibe with
you guys cuz I lately been just doing
game streams, right? And
why is there police sound?
What?
Okay, let's go. I believe I'm not taking
my watcher with me. Should I just take
this bag with me? Why can't I? I could,
but I don't know. I I'll just take it.
[__] it. Yeah,
he's back.
Look at me now. What the?
Let me just lock my door.
Okay.
So, we are going on an adventure. D.
It's so cold outside. It's literally
21°.
It's [__] cold right now. And I'm
here
uh with just a hoodie and some jeans. I
think Yeah, jeans. Yeah. And a bag which
has my water bottle.
I can like show around. We're literally
in the night. Look at the moon. D. You
can't see the moon properly because of
my camera quality, but you can literally
see the stars. If you look closely,
there's twinkling stars.
Yeah, if you look closely, there's
twinkling twinkling stars,
which is really nice and quiet.
It gives you a good vibe.
honestly.
But yeah, so
today is going to be a chatting stream.
Just wanted to chat a bit about things
and my mind and everything lately. So
Danny, so you might have noticed that I
have not streamed for one week
and three or four days. I guess I've
lost account.
I haven't streamed for a while. the show
commen
I
I had a lot of things
had to look at
and do and everything
because of that I
basically couldn't um
do
stuff properly or
and
can say
cuz of that I couldn't uh do stuff. So
I've been uh prioritizing on some side
quests which are
really not that necessary
but I had to do it anyway. So I had been
doing those for a while
and today in a way those got over and
done with. So I'm really really happy
that those stuff the side quest I've
been on are done.
But you know
apparently these two weeks this week and
last week was actually a long vacation
for me
cuz of fall. It's autumn season right
now. So, I got my fall break
actually
and
you know I
I could say this break I was supposed to
stream so much. I was supposed to do a
lot of things but yeah I think I took a
break actually.
I rather than streaming I was working on
the side these side quests which are
necessary for the stream so I can
do streams like right now and everything
right these outdoor streams and
everything so I don't need to for worry
too much about stuff everything is
automated
though it took me like 15 minutes to set
up a stream cuz I stream on five
platforms
But there's that. I'll have to do
something about that. But yeah, um yeah.
So
um I hope I'm still live. Do let me
know, okay? If I'm when my stream cuts
off, if my internet dies, if it says
waiting for video, anything like that,
please do let me know. There would be
like a bit rate issue or like a latency
issue.
as well. But do let me know. Okay. Hi.
What was I? Where? Where was I?
Yeah. Lately, we've been doing Warog.
The joke.
War dogs has been really fun. It was
really nice.
And I want to I wish to come back to
that game. It's fun.
Yeah.
Then, yeah, out of nowhere,
I got busy with work, part-time job,
everything. Even though it was vacation,
I was supposed to enjoy and stuff, but
Uh, am I live? Hello. Hello. Hello.
Am I live?
Okay, I'm live again, bro.
Right when I was going to talk about
something important, my this app crashed
or this did not send the feed to uh
stream.
Yeah.
N
So, um
where do I start actually?
Yeah, I lost my cycle.
which I bought from school store.
I bought that cycle with uh on the
second day after I no not second day,
second day of school actually. Second or
third day of school if I recall
correctly
on a Tuesday.
And guess what?
It was on a Tuesday that I lost it.
It was on a Tuesday that I actually lost
it.
So, somebody stole my cycle from my
apartment.
Uh, we have a cycle parking area.
Somebody stole my cycle.
That day on Tuesday, I was like tired
from coming back from work. It was
raining.
It was raining like hell.
And
it was really raining like hell. And
it was raining like hell and um I was so
tired that I didn't even bother locking
it. It's totally my fault. But but still
I was I still wonder they're like really
cool looking expensive
bicycles out there in that area. All
these other students who have these
crazy uh cool looking bicycles
janchas and stuff. Why a school cycle
bro? Why a cycle which looks literally
like an ordinary cycle? literally had
yellow cycle which there's so many
copies like there were like seven cycles
which has a yellow color same thing same
motor why mine bro
and due to that today
had to walk
from 8 a.m. to
10 a.m. to my water place. I was 1 hour
late
and had to come back walk for two hours.
And today I went to the police station
and reported it like a few like uh two
hours ago, two or three hours ago at
night cuz I was so tired from walking
and walking like 8 kilometers dio 8 or 7
kilometers today. I was so tired. Then I
was like, "Okay,
this vibe is great. It's cold outside at
night. I see the stars and everything."
I haven't streamed every single day,
right?
Since I I know I've been haven't been
streaming for one week and three days,
honestly, each of those days in back of
my head, I'm like, I want to stream. I
miss everyone. I miss my concert plates.
I miss my concerters. I miss everyone. I
miss I miss the people who come by talk
with me.
And I was like,
I don't know what to do. I can't do it.
But I want to do it moment.
And most of the time I uh realized that
I didn't want to stream because how
tired I can I am and I didn't want to
give you guys like a tired dog where you
guys are coming in. I wanting to find
entertainment and make
and be smiley
and I want to do that.
So that's my reasoning.
So
today I just wanted to yap yap
about life and everything. So then even
though it can be seen as me yapping and
just going around rampart about random
things or this and that this and that
wish but
Speaking of which, there's a vending
machine up there.
What the [__] is that sound?
What the What was that sound right now?
What?
It sounded like a UFO. What the hell? Or
an airplane or something. What the hell?
Okay, that's a
It does give you a horror vibe, right?
The green light or something. It's
actually white. My phone makes it look
like it's like like a
back room thingy. Oh yeah, we're going
to that random mission right over there.
Why does it feel like a horror vibe,
bro? Why Why is it with my camera night
mode? What the hell?
What the hell?
Wait, wait. They removed the Coca-Cola.
No, they're What the hell?
No, they removed the Coca-Cola.
Yeah. No, they removed the Coca-Cola.
No,
they actually removed it,
bro. They actually removed it.
This tomato juice though.
Lemon squash. I wonder how that tastes
like.
Wait,
I should have one.
Okay, I think I do have one second.
Wait, why am I suffering? I can just
swipe a card.
Yeah. Apparently, I was given some
money,
financial support from my family just to
buy a cycle somehow
cuz without a cycle, I have to walk
and be tired and it will affect
the timings and everything and it is
rough
honestly.
God, I got scared. Apparently, Japanese
people like to play music while they're
riding their cycles.
That's really cool to see.
Yeah, I'm going to buy this green one,
which looks like
lemon squash.
Hi.
Okay, it's ready.
But I'll just put my card back.
One second.
Okay,
there's a camera over there. Hello.
Okay.
Yeah, this is lemon. So, lemon squash or
something.
That's what it right was written over
here. You know, I don't know how it
tastes. It was yaku 100 yen.
So, let's drink it, I guess.
I'm turning off camera for now. Um,
my
hands are so cold, bro.
It's so windy and so cold.
Ying
after so long. Yeah, unfortunately I
can't stay longer today. It's okay with
I'm just streaming for 1 hour today. I'm
just going to go sleep. It's 12.
I even though I started late. I have to
go sleep. I don't have my cycle. I got
my cycle got stolen recently.
So I have to walk 2 kilo uh no I have to
walk for 2 hours in the morning like
from 7 to yeah if I leave at 7 I'll
reach by 9 and I can be on time for work
so that I have two part-time jobs
tomorrow.
Uh so
I'm going to be super tired but I'll try
my best to see if I can stream. Okay.
So,
it is so nice to just walk,
right?
It is hard to like stabilize your phone,
you know, when I get enough. I'm
currently saving up to buy build a
streaming PC so it can handle streams
and everything.
So, especially game streams and
everything. I want a high quality stuff
there
that kind of um I feel like
I feel like I would um after that I will
try to save up for like a stabilizer or
something.
This cold drink tastes like smells like
medicine, bro.
What?
This smells like a medicine. What is
melon squash?
What the hell?
Oh god, it's medicine. Oh god, it's
medicine. Oh god, it's medicine.
Oh god, it's medicine. Oh god,
this uh this tastes like those English
medicines.
I I'll tell you it's like you you know
the one you take for common cold like
cold and stuff that red liquid medicine
which has that weird taste and has that
after after taste.
Yeah, that one. That one
must be nice staying in a cold country.
It is rough though. I never experienced
snowfall or snow or touch snow. So, I'm
excited for December, but it's going to
go negative degrees over here. So, I'm
I'm scared how that would be.
Your genders are a real mystery for me
to be honest. Yeah,
think of it like this. Um, Remuru
Tempest. It's like the character-wise,
Darknings does not have a gender. It's
more like a uh it's a genderless
androgyny character. It's more like a
it's it's given a vessel or like a shell
a humanoid shell and it's become the
human version is what you're looking at
but I was I'm a boy a bit confusing
voice I guess I'm born with this it's so
it's so it's it's so nice to like see uh
the mystery now. Wait, did I just did I
just ruin the impression?
Oh my god, I just ruined it. [__] man.
What the hell?
It's 60° here at night. Yeah, but
yeah, don't mind it.
Mystery is a mystery.
I keep I keep messing up the thing. I
keep forgetting that jock is jock. Me is
me. I mean, both are me, but yeah. God,
it feels like I'm ringing my
Yeah, boy.
I saw your shadow.
Yeah, but it my shadow does look like Oh
[__] there's a there's a glass thingy.
Oh my god, I just go.
Bro,
bro, did you see that? Did you see? I
almost
if he did not see me. Oh, bro, I would
have died right there. What the hell?
Did you see that? The van did not see
me. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my
god. Oh my god. Oh. Oh my god. Oh my
god. Oh my god. What the [__]
Wait. Did he not see the mirror?
Oh, you are seeing my shadow.
Yeah, this is the this thing
the mailbox you see in anime. It's real.
The mailbox you see in anime. It's real
though.
God, there's no one in the streets. I
feel like an odd one.
Yeah, boy. That is so nice.
Are you a ghost?
You never know.
I love empty streets. Yeah, that's why I
wanted to stream. It's so nice.
It's so nice to just chill and park and
like show you the view of an empty
street
of Aaka.
What is that stuff? Is that like
that's a sheet, right? I I for a second
I was like is that an alien goo which is
like shiny and like it's like going
berber over there.
What am I even saying?
Yeah, that's just a
plastic sheet.
Yeah, it's so nice, Diana. I wish you
can experience the cold and everything.
You can hear from my mic phone mic right
the insects or the cicatas which are
uh crying out loud
or like singing maybe they're not crying
they're singing
the chirping you can say
sometime
another vending machine
and wait that is like a graffiti TV
show. Nothing over there.
Yeah.
Yeah. I
Where do I go? I'll just go straight
then.
I can I can just go straight. Yeah.
It's such a beautiful country. I'm glad
I'm not in Tokyo. Tokyo at this time it
would be uh too crowded or something.
That would be people. I mean,
do is all about night life and
everything.
Look at that area. Those areas.
God, there's moths right now. There was
a little moth which tried to
tried to touch the phone and I just
shoot it away.
Yeah. So nice though.
I'm just drinking my lemon squash, which
is which tastes literally like
medicine.
But honestly though, regarding IIL
setups, IRL streams like this, I one day
wish to like switch to an IL setup.
Uh there there is this JP streamer. They
they they do have a VTuber model or like
a VTuber PNG.
They like go out for jogging. I just saw
them today like on Twitch.
Um
and
I want to ask them so many things, man.
And I want to be active in their
community and be like ask them like what
do you do about the internet situation
when you're outdoors?
Which mobile sim connection do you have?
I don't ask that cuz some areas
Why don't you take coffee or something?
Ah,
you're right. No, no, no. I'm supposed
to go sleep in a bit.
I have to go sleep. I have to wake up in
6 hours.
6 or 5 hours.
I have to go for work
part time. I don't I don't have a cycle.
So, I have to walk to work today.
Come back, take a rest, go for the
second part-time job,
take a train, come back. home by 1000
p.m. or something or 9:30 p.m. or
something, then probably there's a
chance I might stream.
Then there's a chance I might not
stream. Who knows?
Yeah.
So, and there's this Buddhist thingy
over here.
This is interesting.
Let's Let's take a walk on the bridge.
Okay.
I want to show you the bridge.
I'm very habitated to coffee that I
don't feel any difference in sleep. The
thing is now if I drink coffee
or tea, it just makes me sleepy.
I have the opposite.
I have the opposite effect. That's
because my body was trained
to see caffeine as sleeping
uh medicine.
That's partly my fault.
That's partly my fault basically
because
back in India, back at home
um
when there was nothing in the house to
eat at night. My family are asleep like
at 12 or 1:00 a.m. or something or 3:00
a.m. I'm still not asleep.
I used to just go to the kitchen and
make some black black tea
and
with sugar and just drink
like three glasses of it and and
go sleep.
And that became a daily routine to the
point that
every time
every time I drink tea or coffee I
feel sleepy.
Is there any racism towards Indians in
it? Depends on which area and which
place you are in.
Uh
if you're in Tokyo,
uh not much I guess
not sure I don't know but not not much
people were racism racist towards me or
xenophobic towards me.
If you are going to Arugawa
Nishi Kasai area where there's a lot of
Indians
maybe
they'll uh kind of be understanding cuz
they see a lot of Indians they know the
Indian nature I guess.
Uh
but some hates Indians I guess from
there.
And yeah, colorbased can be there too.
Most of the time now if it's colorbased
most people think you're from Sri Lanka
or Nepal or something like that
or some of the times yeah they tell like
are you from Assam or are you from India
or something like that.
for this
and um
I don't know. Oh yeah, this is the place
right there.
There were like few Japanese people
looking at me like why is there a person
holding a phone and walking towards the
bridge with like a can in his hand.
They were like scared or something.
They're looking at me. I'm scared that I
feel self-conscious, man.
It's Yeah. Yeah. There's so much uh
stuff like that now online too.
It is so nice to like
look at this. No, it's so nice.
That is nice.
Why am I coming here?
I kind of know. Don't dive. Don't jump.
Lol.
No, I'm not going to jump, bro. My life
is not over yet.
Not not going to end my life until I
succeed with my dreams. That's why I'm
here at the show.
Uh they are I I shine the brightest.
That's the day
my goal has been completed.
My son, you're telling me to jump off
that bridge. dawned.
I just wanted you to see the waves of
the ocean and stuff. Look at the waves
though. It's so nice to just look at
this. But you cannot stand still like
this. People will misunderstand.
That's why we going to sit over there in
that light area.
Yeah.
Bacon. Don't be scared.
Hello bacon. Hi every
properly. I don't think I can see it
properly. I need to find a different
route
which can give a give me a closer look
at the thingy. But yeah, one day I want
to swim here or something.
I I know a place. It's under the bridge.
Similar similar to like this
under the bridge of my school area, I
guess. Um you can actually go down and
like uh sneak towards the river bank
thingy.
I want to buy it. I'll just wait till
sales. Yeah, but the thing is what dog
now they might increase the price in the
future though
the dev said that they're going to
increase the price from
uh I think it's 40 right 40 to 60 like
that more the more it becomes better
the game you know
jump in and swim not now but someday
Yeah, look at this.
I can like
it is so close by.
The issue is not I'm literally alone
and there's no one here. I'm literally
in the dark.
God knows if a boogeyman comes.
There's so many things, right? Why am I
night exploring like this?
Who knows?
If I'm watching your stream,
wait, really? Let's go,
V. Let's go. But
but
but to be honest though, am I supposed
to be here
at this point of time?
Uh it it happens for just chatting
streams if I'm correct.
Sometimes
sometimes you get it for just chatting
streams
apparently.
The vibe is so cold though.
Working two do jobs now. Quite chill.
Wait, you're working two jobs?
Should I even walk over there? It's so
scary, man.
Ah, the night.
Imagine if there's a warden or something
over here. They'll just scold me. All
right.
N
Why is there a staircase over there?
Tina.
Okay.
Oh, you're not supposed to sit here.
Uh,
the thing is now places like this, it's
scary cuz you never know what can
happen.
Is that a bicycle over there? Bro, it's
giving me strange weird vibes. I'm going
to go turn back. No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm just going to fall back. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, yada yada yada yada
yada.
Yada yada yada yada yada. I'm just
getting creepy vibes. I'm just getting
creepy vibes.
My body is shaking,
bro. Why am I thinking so?
Oh god,
that's a toilet.
Why the [__] is there a cycle there?
Come on.
Yeah, I should be care more careful when
coming alone like this.
Especially since I I got my cycle
stolen. If I see stuff like that, I'm
get I get scared now.
I
God. Oh my god. Why did I think of this
horror horror stuff? Every single thing
is making me scared. I hate horror.
I want to go home.
Oh my god. I want to just go home.
Why? Why?
Bro, what is that thing? Did you see a
face
mate? M.
Do you see that?
That looked like someone's face. What
the [__]
That looked like someone's face. That is
someone's face. Okay.
Oh my god.
But the wave is so nice to show.
Hello. Hello.
Ah,
why are you so nice?
This man
didn't sign.
Oh, yeah. You're not able to see though.
Do you see how far that is?
That's so far down.
And there's rocks at the bottom.
Goodbye, man.
Uh, the river.
Wait, who remembers the
Wait, do you guys remember? I don't
know. Most of you are guys are new,
right? I used to. There was a time I
used to do a stream near the ocean back
in India. Uh
yeah, that time I had my PC
uh that was audio only.
There there was never visual, but there
were times I showed like the video of it
of me going to the uh beach and stuff,
drawing uh names of everyone in the sand
and everything. Yeah, these kites just
remind me of that. That's true.
Long back ago.
on there.
It's so nice.
A rocker in the sky. Nco.
I would be living the time of my life if
I was there.
That's one way to get killed.
Oh yeah, Sukia is here.
The usual Sukia.
As you can see, it's isn't a moon biso.
They send out some people to space
station.
Why are people looking at me? Is it
weird that uh that uh a guy like a
foreigner is literally walking past a
bridge
at 12:30 a.m.
on a Thursday?
No, it's a Friday. It's Friday. It's
Friday, everyone. I forgot it's Friday.
for me.
It's Friday for me.
Oh, wait. You can see this
the tow truck thingy.
Oh, that's so cool as well.
This is how they transport goods to
restaurants and stuff
in there.
I see cycles park there.
Thanks for thanks for the little stream.
See you later. Hi. Thank you all for
coming by.
Thank you for coming by.
Have a good one.
Wow.
Oh, dog. It's spooky month. How was your
first day? Will you watch a horror movie
or
I forgot it's October?
The month I hate so much
because it's Halloween.
I cannot handle horror. That's why I
retreated just a while ago cuz it felt
like a horror movie kind of thingy.
There was a abandoned cycle over there
and I my cycle got stolen recently and
I was like scared like is it abandoned
or is it someone there or is someone
doing something bad or sussy?
God knows.
Uh but yeah,
one day now I'll come here and wash my
clothes.
This coin
coin laundry place in here is so nice.
Hey
Bakasi vas. Yeah.
What happened? Nothing.
Uh
I was talking about how October is
it's October now. It's the month of
Oh yeah, it's a month of um what do you
call it?
You got to play uh do horror stuff,
right?
Oh, yeah. Apparently this lemon thingy
is really good. Gives you that oomph
thingy.
It's better that they have than that.
This water lemon thingy.
This is pure lemon extract.
Uh my roommate bought that and it's
really good.
It gives it gives you that kick you need
just to even if you are sleepy, you want
to get to home uh quicker. You just take
a couple of sips of that. You get that
energy for a bit.
Yeah.
So,
okay, I'll just I think I can cut the IO
string
camera thingy for a bit. Now,
we'll switch to a singer. Go.
Yeah.
I mean, the camera is here, so don't
worry. It's red light.
But yeah, it's been a while I used this
app to stream the show.
But yeah, it is fun.
So, how has been everyone lately?
How has been everyone lately there?
Uh,
I want to do a lot of things, but I
can't do a lot of things.
God, I was almost going to show my
phone to my to a mirror. There was a
reflective area. Oh my god. Thank god I
turned off the camera. Ah, I was so
careless right now. You ate dinner? Yes,
I did. So,
Oh, yeah. I forgot to mention I am
partaking in a tournament
uh called Pure Championship
something.
Uh
so I'm not sure about the lineup and the
themes and everything.
I have to learn about the game.
Yeah,
a friend of mine told me about it
and I was like, hm, interesting.
I'll
uh I'll try it out
and see.
The the rewards is like 50,000 yen.
That's like basically,
if I'm correct,
uh
40,000 rupees I guess
I think not sure
but if 15 is 15
thou 15,000 rupees is 20
25,000
yen I believe it's around 20 or 25 or
30,000 rupees
the c the refiner rewards.
But if it's a team, I believe it's a
team based thingy. So,
so probably
it's going to
be splitted with your teammates
and stuff.
So, there's that.
I got scared for a second, bro.
What is that?
What's that? It's a some pew pew thingy.
Um I forgot the name properly, but it's
called pew pew.
Um
30,55459.
Hi. Thank you.
Yeah, that much.
And I mean it's a tournament hosted by
Vakon
India.
Yeah. I I'll see how that goes. Hope it
goes well.
Speaking of tournaments though, I want
to join like Apex tournaments. There's
so many local land tournaments
happening. not local land, but more like
local
uh I mean Japanese YouTubers are hosting
so many uh Apex Legends
uh tournaments and I want to try them
out.
I do want to
I do want to like
participate
but I need a team now.
That's the hard part.
Woohoo.
No friends.
I need I need I need like if it's a
local tournament, mostly people from
Japan and stuff,
I need to find a Japanese teammate.
If if like other regions are allowed,
I want to bring bac I want to bring
bacon.
So, Bacon is good at FPS,
aren't you? I don't know if you're here,
but yeah, you're good at FPS, man. You
have carried me in Arc Raiders. I
haven't forgotten the moments.
Oh god. Yeah. Also, speaking of Arc
Raiders, the new update is nice.
They changed a lot of things. I want to
come back to
our creators.
What? New donation from Bacon. What?
Thank you for donating.
You have carried me. You have given me
so much reactor course. Bastion bastion
cell this and that. Help me do the
expedition ones.
Yeah.
Yeah. I couldn't do it without Shivik. I
still remember those.
Even if I don't play.
Oh, why am I so sleepy? I Yeah, it's
almost going to be 1:00 a.m. Well, even
if I don't play our creators anymore,
but yeah, I still remember the moments.
Wow, I wish I had made clips of it or
something. Wow. Wait. Yeah, there were
times we were off off stream playing.
I'm stuck at that was just PBE. I'm
stuck at marathon. Yeah, marathon, too.
I have to get back into that game. I
paid for that game. Speaking of paid
games, uh, Sword Art
Hornline, that game. Oh my god, I paid
for that game. I'm not even playing.
Well, well, that's so much things.
And that is what it is.
Extreme
dashboard.
Yeah. So many things.
Wait. Uh tier 2 subs now get access to
gifts in chat.
footage.
Wow, that's interesting.
Hey,
let's go.
Uh, I'm getting back into Battlefield 6.
Ah, nice. Nice.
Yeah, Battle Six. Battlefield 6 was
cheap for 3 days
when Warogs was launched. I wanted to
buy it. Then I was like conflicted like
uh will I even play Battlefield 6?
So I chose not to
chose not to buy it.
Now I kind of regret
that choice. Now to wait when it's like
cheap again or on a sale again.
Thank you. Thank you Bacon for becoming
an astral constellation.
Thank you for becoming a member for 17
months.
Wow. Thank you. Thank you.
So, so many things.
But yeah, uh I can't wait for next
month.
Next month I'll have my stream PC.
Next month I'll have my stream PC, bro.
Ah,
but it's not all fun and games. But
still I just wish there won't be any
issues
like the graphics card, the motherboard,
the power, no mother graphics card,
uh the graphics card, the capture card,
the motherboard and RAM
and my SSD.
My sensei uh from India is going to
bring them my my dad will be packing
them and like giving it to my sensei and
sensei will be bringing it to me. So
I'll just have to collect it and then
build it. I I found like a PC cabinet PC
case and I just have to buy PC case,
power supply and a cooler.
Yeah, that's about it. and some uh cable
stuff. Um HDMI cable thingy then
display port to
USB C
or something. But yeah,
from where? Oh my um yeah, it's going to
come from India.
My sense from India who taught me
Japanese from India.
uh he's coming he's in India right now.
He's going to come back
to Japan
uh next month. I mean the end of this
month. So I asked him like can you bring
my stuff if possible?
Uh and he was like yeah sure.
So I'm like excited. I just have to save
up a little bit of money even though I'm
really broke and tight.
Um, yeah. I just have to save up and
build the thing.
Yeah, finally I can play games with no
lag on the on the laptop.
Uh,
I can finally play Warog with no lag,
bro.
I don't have to worry about stuff.
And it will look like
high FPS game play.
God, I'm I'm over overinking over over
like I'm manifesting it.
I mean, those who have watched me before
the body cam stream last two years back,
you know how the game play and
everything would be.
cuz I've used uh G um the display C uh
the the capture card dual PC setup for
like two or three years or two years.
Ever since I got it, bought it. I know
upgraded it.
I still done it.
Yeah. Oh, speaking of which, Witcher 3
remaster result. No, I want to play
Witcher. Uh, but sad thing is that I
never bought Witcher, so I have to pay
so much money to buy play it. Wow.
Should have bought it when it was just
$2 though. I'm so dumb.
Never expected that. A Witcher 3 is
going to get a race master.
Never expected that. Oh, yeah. Wow.
Someone is getting in trouble. There's
police.
Can you hear that? Oh, it's so windy and
cold.
Yeah. Yeah. It's so cold.
It's so cold.
Yeah. Bye.
I know jaw.
Oh god.
Watch to open a green gray ball.
this Pokemon thingy on just chatting
category. I never expected that.
That is interesting. Honestly,
anyway, it's going to be um 1 hour. It's
going to be what uh
1 hour 30 minutes or something.
So, we'll wrap it up. Okay, before I
wrap up, I'll just say some uh these are
kind of non uh non-necessary, but feel
free to listen if you want to, but it's
all good. Okay, so uh for those who
don't know, I have a VOD channel
uh jocknick_247
on uh on Twitch and YouTube and uh
YouTube. It's the what's jocknick what's
channel and uh twitch and kick it's
jocknick 247.
Um so I recently was able to these are
the side quests I spoke of in the
beginning of the stream. I recently
switched everything to the cloud. So
every 14 days two weeks that's two
weeks. Every two weeks there's a new
content cycle.
So every two weeks there's going to be a
new playlist of content, old jocknik
content. It can be new, old, random
content which will be played all
throughout.
Uh yeah, feel free to uh check out the
more channel if you are free, if you
want to just watch older content and
stuff. It's going to be always be
playing like a TV show or a radio
thingy. So, feel free to check it out. I
finally was able to switch everything. I
do need to make some optimization for
that event though. Other than that, it's
all good. Yeah.
Other than that, it's all good. So also
didn't need to make some optimization
though.
Yeah. I mean I really I believe it's
live right now but yeah I just need to
restart the stream. I mean I mean I did
restart the stream but yeah.
So yeah there's that. Then what else did
I do? Also the website. my website. I
made a little bit of titsy updates to
the website. There's now new guidelines
and rules.
Uh, and it's now readable.
It's it's way easier to read now rather
than a whole encyclopedia in one page
like in the past. Now it's more easier
and section sectionable.
can read it properly. Uh it's split in
different sections and stuff. Same with
the information page as well. And
finally, we have a footer on my website.
Finally,
finally have a footer page. So, you can
see all my socials. I have I changed the
menu thingy. The homepage, it has some
twinkling stars. He He Yeah, it has a
stars background thingy. I'm still
upgrading it. Okay, I'm still upgrading
it. I still want to switch to the New
York Jo Nexus theme team theme. Astral
Astroen astral constellation theme. I
have to like slowly do that. It'll take
some time.
So then but yeah.
So yeah. What else?
Yeah, if you seen uh Twitter
uh if you type https
or like dolink.space on Discord, you get
a mini profile of
uh like a custom Discord
only mini profile.
Discord component mini profile thingy.
Yeah. Yeah, I did that too.
I plan to make custom uh embedded
components for uh some
of the pages
some pages.
I do have some plans for that. So yeah,
that's a lot. That's uh most of
everything I wanted to show you. It's
one hour 1 hour 27 minutes.
So,
thank you to each and every one of you
who came by today. All the people who
came by today are let me read every one
of your names. Bre, thank you for coming
by.
Uh, Mikasuki, Rich for coming by.
Konadasan, thank you for coming by. Uh,
oh god, it's so windy.
Bacon, thank you for coming by.
Uh Risha, thank you for coming by.
Callisan, thank you for coming by.
Um that's everyone.
Thank you again, Bacon, for the donation
on Kofi and thank you for becoming an
astral constellation
YouTube member. Thank you.
With that said, I mean I will
that said I will wrap it up for here.
Thank you for coming by. I'll see you
guys in the next stream. Okay. Hi. I'll
promise you
guys, but I'll try my best to stream
more, okay?
Cuz you know,
out of everything, I love streaming so
much. Something I'm passionate about.
So, I'm going to keep on streaming.
Let me show you this
going
Can you even see the stars?
I hope it shine the brightest like the
stars up in the sky.
What's the joke? And bye-bye.
Heat. Heat.
Hey. Hey. Hey.